[{"_id":"5f39c35f67894200172a5a42","question":"What is the first book of the Bible?","correct":"Genesis","wrong1":"Exodus","wrong2":"Psalms","wrong3":"Deuteronomy","difficulty":"easy","__v":0},{"_id":"5f3c0955b0887500172e7dd0","question":"What did God say to Noah about the ark?","correct":"Go into the ark and bring your family and male and female of event species.","wrong1":"Gi in and seal yourself in.","wrong2":"Go in and bring all your friends and family/","wrong3":"I have changed my mind and will not flood the earth.","difficulty":"easy","__v":0},{"_id":"5f3c0a89b0887500172e7dd1","question":"Who was Moses’ brother?","correct":"Aaron","wrong1":"Joshua","wrong2":"Samuel","wrong3":"Joseph","difficulty":"medium","__v":0},{"_id":"5f3c0b7cb0887500172e7dd2","question":"Which book in the Old Testament tells the 10 Commandments?","correct":"Exodus 20","wrong1":"Genesis","wrong2":"Job","wrong3":"Psakms","difficulty":"hard","__v":0},{"_id":"5f3c0bf1b0887500172e7dd3","question":"How many books are in the Protestant Old and New Testaments?","correct":"66","wrong1":"100","wrong2":"23","wrong3":"10","difficulty":"medium","__v":0},{"_id":"5f3c0fa9b0887500172e7dd4","question":"Name 2 Mary’s who were present with Jesus at His Crucifixion.","correct":"Mary the Mother of God and Mary Magdalene","wrong1":"Queen Mary and Angel Mary","wrong2":"Mary of Judaehand Mary Bathsheba","wrong3":"His 2 sisters","difficulty":"easy","__v":0},{"_id":"5f3c10a0b0887500172e7dd5","question":"According to Jesus which Commandmenr is the most important?","correct":"Love the Lord Your God with all your God with all your heart.","wrong1":"Do not lie.","wrong2":"Easter will be on Sunday.","wrong3":"Never love money.","difficulty":"medium","__v":0},{"_id":"5f3c1116b0887500172e7dd6","question":"Who was swallowed by a giant fish?","correct":"Jonah","wrong1":"Ezra","wrong2":"Nehemiah","wrong3":"Job","difficulty":"easy","__v":0},{"_id":"5f3c11f8b0887500172e7dd7","question":"What are the names of the four Gospels?","correct":"Matthew, Mark, Luke, and John","wrong1":"Matthew, Romans, Acts, and Revelations","wrong2":"1 John, 2 John, 3 John, and Peter","wrong3":"Luke, John, Acts, and Paul","difficulty":"easy","__v":0},{"_id":"5f3c12c2b0887500172e7dd8","question":"In what book do tongues of fire alight on the disciples?","correct":"Acts","wrong1":"Revelation","wrong2":"Light unto the World","wrong3":"Promethius","difficulty":"easy","__v":0},{"_id":"5f3d982afdc7070017aea407","question":"Who walked on water with Jesus","correct":"Peter","wrong1":"Judas","wrong2":"John the Baptist","wrong3":"Paul","difficulty":"easy","__v":0},{"_id":"5f3d9bb0fdc7070017aea408","question":"How far did Jesus walk with the cross?","correct":"2000 feet or 600 meters","wrong1":"1 mile","wrong2":"500 feet","wrong3":"1500 meters","difficulty":"hard","__v":0},{"_id":"5f3d9c33fdc7070017aea409","question":"What mountain was Jesus crucified on?","correct":"Golgatha or Calgary","wrong1":"Mt. Carmel","wrong2":"Mt. Sinai","wrong3":"Mt. Nebo","difficulty":"medium","__v":0},{"_id":"5f3d9c8afdc7070017aea40a","question":"Which son of Noah did Jesus come from?","correct":"Shem","wrong1":"Ham","wrong2":"Japeth","wrong3":"Cannan","difficulty":"medium","__v":0},{"_id":"5f3d9cc7fdc7070017aea40b","question":"On what mountain was Jesus crucified?","correct":"Golgatha or Calvary","wrong1":"Sinai","wrong2":"Nebo","wrong3":"Herman","difficulty":"medium","__v":0}]